<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>ask_for_clarification_on_an_assignment</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ask for Clarification on an Assignment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;Whenever Tao&amp;rsquo;s
boss assigns him a project, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t give him enough details on what&amp;rsquo;s
needed. But Tao worries that if he asks for more information, he&amp;rsquo;ll seem incompetent.
A professional coach explains how to get the information you need&amp;mdash;even from the
busiest of bosses&amp;mdash;to excel at an assignment.&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;Coach&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lauren Mackler&lt;/b&gt; is an internationally renowned executive and life coach, bestselling author, and keynote speaker. Over the past 25 years she&amp;rsquo;s been a psychotherapist, corporate executive, leader of Arthur Andersen&amp;rsquo;s Human Capital consulting practice, and a leading authority in human behavior, leadership, and professional performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lauren&amp;rsquo;s the author of the international bestseller &amp;ldquo;Solemate: Master the Art of Aloneness &amp;amp; Transform Your Life,&amp;rdquo; and contributor to &amp;ldquo;Speaking of Success&amp;rdquo; with Stephen Covey, Ken Blanchard, and Jack Canfield. Her work is frequently featured in the media, including CNN, FOX, the Wall Street Journal, the Huffington Post, the London Daily Mail, the Boston Globe, and the Boston Business Journal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tao Yang&lt;/b&gt; does everything that interests him with the flourish and dedication of a wonk, meaning that he is a data-wonk, improv-wonk, and computer-wonk. Tao is one of the hardest-working young comedy improvisers in the field. By day he is a data analyst at a healthcare information services company. By night he performs at ImprovBoston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tao started doing improv with Boston University&amp;rsquo;s Liquid Fun and taking classes at ImprovBoston. He graduated from BU and from ImprovBoston. He has been selected to join the cast of &amp;ldquo;Face Off,&amp;rdquo; and appears with his ImprovBoston team at Big Gulp 40 on the weekends. When he has the time, his usual schedule of studying, performing, and learning improv often consumes eight hours of his day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;My approach to comedy is to never stop learning.&amp;rdquo; Tao seems to be living up to his own words on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Alex LeBaron&lt;/b&gt; is an actor, improviser, writer, and instructor currently residing in Chicago. He is a founding member of Rich Uncle and has performed with the sketch groups Whippersnapper, Mosaic, and the Ruckus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex has appeared in numerous showcase shows, including: &amp;ldquo;Love Seasonally,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Wheel of Austen,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;T: An MBTA Musical,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;1.21 Jigowatts,&amp;rdquo; Manthorne and the Baron,&amp;rdquo; Gorefests IX and X, and &amp;ldquo;Playbook.&amp;rdquo; He has performed various shows at Duofest, Providence Improv Festival, Del Close Marathon, Philadelphia Improv Festival, and the North Carolina ComedyArts Festival. As First Person Interpreter at Bostonian Society, he presented historical materials to crowds of up to 75 in an educational and entertaining manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex received his Bachelor of Arts in international affairs and political science at the University of New Hampshire. He studied Spanish language and literature at the Pontificia Universidad Cat&amp;oacute;lica de Valpara&amp;iacute;so.&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_brn07s25</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_2wcescn4</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_b7bs26qg</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>