<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>how_to_talk_with_your_boss_about_work_overload</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to Talk with Your Boss About Work Overload&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Brendan expresses worry about his heavy workload to his boss, Robert. But Robert doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem concerned&amp;mdash;or supportive. A professional coach reveals how Robert can effectively manage his own workload&amp;mdash;starting with getting help from Robert to prioritize his projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;Coach&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lauren Mackler &lt;/b&gt;is an internationally renowned executive and life coach, bestselling author, and keynote speaker. Over the past 25 years she&amp;rsquo;s been a psychotherapist, corporate executive, leader of Arthur Andersen&amp;rsquo;s Human Capital consulting practice, and a leading authority in human behavior, leadership, and professional performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lauren&amp;rsquo;s the author of the international bestseller &amp;ldquo;Solemate: Master the Art of Aloneness &amp;amp; Transform Your Life,&amp;rdquo; and contributor to &amp;ldquo;Speaking of Success&amp;rdquo; with Stephen Covey, Ken Blanchard, and Jack Canfield. Her work is frequently featured in the media, including CNN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;FOX, the Wall Street Journal, the Huffington Post, the London Daily Mail, the Boston Globe, and the Boston Business Journal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Actors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brendan Mulhern&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; is an actor, improviser, and musician. He has worked with ImprovBoston since 2008 and is currently a member of their National Touring Company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Brendan co-created the two-man improv show &amp;ldquo;Manthorne and The Baron,&amp;rdquo; which ran during ImprovBoston&amp;rsquo;s Comedy Lab. &amp;nbsp;The production became a Showcase Show featured at Philly Duofest, Del Close Marathon in New York City, and the 3rd Annual Boston Comedy Arts Festival. His Boston theater credits include: &amp;ldquo;The Haberdasher: A Tale of Derring-Do, &amp;ldquo;The Seabirds&amp;rdquo; (Argos Productions); &amp;ldquo;Deathtrap&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Money Python&amp;rsquo;s Spamalot&amp;rdquo; (The Company Theater); and &amp;ldquo;T: An MBTA Musical&amp;rdquo; (A.R.T./Club Oberon). Film credits include &amp;ldquo;A Terrible Idea&amp;rdquo; (MMM Productions) and &amp;ldquo;The Heebie-Jeebies&amp;rdquo; (Dust Bunny Productions).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Robert Woo&lt;/b&gt; is the Marketing Manager at InsightSquared. A student of viral marketing and comedy, his goal is to mesh these two aspects at every turn in his professional career. Robert tries comedy in improv currently with Hard Left Productions, and stand-up currently in front of a mirror. He writes sketches and web series; acts for various commercials; directs improv off and on; and plays the guitar just enough to maintain his calluses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Robert has performed in various festivals in Boston, Lowell, Chicago, New York, Providence, Sarasota, Tokyo, Atlanta, Lowell, Vancouver, and Austin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Robert studied at Tufts University.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_s3qgqq9p</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_ke2z7wr1</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_82ydetlj</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>