<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>how_to_handle_rumors_that_a_valued_employee_may_leave</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">How to Handle Rumors that a Valued Employee May Leave</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;Marcelo&amp;rsquo;s
heard that Christine, an exemplary employee, plans to leave the company. He
confronts her&amp;mdash;including trying to make her feel guilty about leaving. She&amp;rsquo;s
shocked by his aggressive approach. A professional coach describes a more
effective response&amp;mdash;starting with finding out if such rumors are even true.&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;Coach&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lauren Mackler
&lt;/b&gt;is an internationally renowned executive and life coach, bestselling author,
and keynote speaker. Over the past 25 years she&amp;rsquo;s been a psychotherapist,
corporate executive, leader of Arthur Andersen&amp;rsquo;s Human Capital consulting
practice, and a leading authority in human behavior, leadership, and
professional performance. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lauren&amp;rsquo;s the
author of the international bestseller &amp;ldquo;Solemate: Master the Art of Aloneness
&amp;amp; Transform Your Life,&amp;rdquo; and contributor to &amp;ldquo;Speaking of Success&amp;rdquo; with
Stephen Covey, Ken Blanchard, and Jack Canfield. Her work is frequently
featured in the media, including CNN&lt;i&gt;, &lt;/i&gt;FOX, the Wall Street Journal, the
Huffington Post, the London Daily Mail, the Boston Globe, and the Boston
Business Journal.&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;Contact Lauren at &lt;a href="http://www.laurenmackler.com."&gt;http://www.laurenmackler.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Marcelo Illarmo&lt;/b&gt;
is a member of ImprovBoston. He is also an associate litigation lawyer with
Sullivan &amp;amp; Worcester LLP who has represented a variety of clients from
small construction firms to Fortune 500 companies. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After performing
with Liquid Fun&amp;rsquo;s inaugural cast at Boston University, Marcelo joined Face Off
(formerly TheatreSports) before his senior year of college. In addition to
performing with Face Off, he has performed in various shows, including a
staging of his one-man show, &amp;ldquo;Tales of a Broken Heart.&amp;rdquo; His favorite memories
of ImprovBoston include hosting the Sunday Night Jam with JR Strauss and
performing an original musical he cowrote in college, &amp;ldquo;Jesus Christ Mega Star.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcelo
graduated from Boston University with a BA, magna cum laude. He attended the
Boston University School of Law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christine Cuddy,
who prefers to be called by her last name, is a seasoned actress. She grew up
in the Boston area, where she trained in the performing arts. She also learned
her trade at the Second City and Annoyance theaters in Chicago. She performs
with the Mainstage cast and teaches improv at ImprovBoston. She writes and
performs in OBV!, a two-woman show with Megan Goltermann, and has appeared in
regional commercials. Christine can be heard on the ImprovBoston podcast with Will
Luera and Harry Gordon. Her favorite festival experience is performing in the
Improv Allstar Show with Rachel Dratch at the Women in Comedy Festival in
Boston.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other
ImprovBoston credits include &amp;ldquo;Cabin Pressure,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The A-Team,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Real
Housewives of the Magick Kingdom,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The Lodge,&amp;rdquo; a three-person show that
plays to her biggest strength--being a townie. Christine has performed at
improv festivals all over the United States, Ireland, and Spain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christine
graduated from Framingham State University with a degree in communication arts
with a focus in acting and directing. &lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_wdqqxd2g</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_9jbdeid8</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_q0lmlbtj</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>