<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>stay_calm_in_a_stressful_moment</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">&lt;span&gt;Stay Calm in a Stressful Moment&lt;/span&gt;</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;News of a restructuring at her company has Christine in a panic. She isolates herself, which only worsens her stress. A professional coach explains how to better manage stress&amp;mdash;including using relaxation techniques and reaching out to others for moral support and &amp;ldquo;reality checks.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coach&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lauren Mackler&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;is an internationally renowned executive and life coach, bestselling author, and keynote speaker. Over the past 25 years she&amp;rsquo;s been a psychotherapist, corporate executive, leader of Arthur Andersen&amp;rsquo;s Human Capital consulting practice, and a leading authority in human behavior, leadership, and professional performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lauren&amp;rsquo;s the author of the international bestseller &amp;ldquo;Solemate: Master the Art of Aloneness &amp;amp; Transform Your Life,&amp;rdquo; and contributor to &amp;ldquo;Speaking of Success&amp;rdquo; with Stephen Covey, Ken Blanchard, and Jack Canfield. Her work is frequently featured in the media, including CNN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;FOX, the Wall Street Journal, the Huffington Post, the London Daily Mail, the Boston Globe, and the Boston Business Journal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Contact Lauren at&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.laurenmackler.com."&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.laurenmackler.com.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Actors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Christine Cuddy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;, who prefers to be called by her last name, is a seasoned actress. She grew up in the Boston area, where she trained in the performing arts. She also learned her trade at the Second City and Annoyance theaters in Chicago. She performs with the Mainstage cast and teaches improv at ImprovBoston. She writes and performs in OBV!, a two-woman show with Megan Goltermann, and has appeared in regional commercials. Christine can be heard on the ImprovBoston podcast with Will Luera and Harry Gordon. Her favorite festival experience is performing in the Improv Allstar Show with Rachel Dratch at the Women in Comedy Festival in Boston. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other ImprovBoston credits include &amp;ldquo;Cabin Pressure,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The A-Team,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Real Housewives of the Magick Kingdom,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The Lodge,&amp;rdquo; a three-person show that plays to her biggest strength--being a townie. Christine has performed at improv festivals all over the United States, Ireland, and Spain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Christine graduated from Framingham State University with a degree in communication arts with a focus in acting and directing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Google &amp;ldquo;Mike Morrell&amp;rdquo; and an American politician, a CIA Deputy Director, and a modern mystic come up before Mike Morrell, actor and improviser, comes into view. Any of these characters are subjects Mike could impersonate with ease. He is the creator/director of &amp;ldquo;Crime Solving Bear&amp;rdquo; and the popular &amp;ldquo;DWA Presents,&amp;rdquo; better known as &amp;ldquo;The Drinking Show.&amp;rdquo; He has filmed over 100 commercials and training videos with roles as varied and diverse as bad nurse, bad paper shredder, and bad employee.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mike has performed improv and stand-up all over Boston, New York, and Los Angeles. He is the cast member of TheartreSports as well as creator and cast member of the showcase show &amp;ldquo;UnAuthorized Biography.&amp;rdquo; He just filmed his first speaking role in a major production.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_ykpa2ifo</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_99qcdiy9</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_mx7vrko2</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>