<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>is_your_boss_a_leader_or_a_listener</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Is Your Boss a Listener or a Reader? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harry&amp;rsquo;s written a detailed report for his boss, Doreen, about a customer management system he&amp;rsquo;s advocating. But when he meets with Doreen to discuss it, she hasn&amp;rsquo;t read his report. Instead, she wants him to talk her through the highlights, and he&amp;rsquo;s not prepared. A professional coach explains how to adapt to Doreen&amp;rsquo;s preferred way of receiving information&amp;mdash;so Harry can communicate far more effectively with her.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coach&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lauren Mackler i&lt;/b&gt;s an internationally renowned executive and life coach, bestselling author, and keynote speaker. Over the past 25 years she&amp;rsquo;s been a psychotherapist, corporate executive, leader of Arthur Andersen&amp;rsquo;s Human Capital consulting practice, and a leading authority in human behavior, leadership, and professional performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lauren&amp;rsquo;s the author of the international bestseller &amp;ldquo;Solemate: Master the Art of Aloneness &amp;amp; Transform Your Life,&amp;rdquo; and contributor to &amp;ldquo;Speaking of Success&amp;rdquo; with Stephen Covey, Ken Blanchard, and Jack Canfield. Her work is frequently featured in the media, including CNN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;FOX, the Wall Street Journal, the Huffington Post, the London Daily Mail, the Boston Globe, and the Boston Business Journal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Actors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harry Gordon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;was born in Vermont and began his performing career when he sang &amp;ldquo;Hard-Hearted Hannah&amp;rdquo; to his grandparents at the age of seven. He is a performer, writer, instructor, and comedian who earned his chops at the Improv Asylum in Boston&amp;rsquo;s North End and ImprovBoston in Cambridge. He hosts the critically acclaimed &amp;ldquo;Harry Roasts America!&amp;rdquo; at ImprovBoston and improvises in a variety of shows and troupes, including Directions. He is an active member of the Greater Boston Zen Center and volunteers for a variety of organizations through them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harry has work experience in a variety of fields, including insurance, investment, higher education, consulting, and transportation. He is a Sales Executive at Zipcar in their Zipcar for Business program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Doreen Collins&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;rsquo; show business career began at the tender age of eight in front of 20,000 people, performing with Diana Ross and the Supremes. Since then, she has been an active member of SAG, AFTRA, and AGVA and has performed Off-Broadway and on television, film, and radio. Doreen&amp;rsquo;s one-woman show &amp;ldquo;BOOZICAL the Musical: The Unorganized Biography of Doreen Collins&amp;rdquo; is proof there is nothing that can embarrass her! She lives to perform. She&amp;rsquo;s the host of &amp;ldquo;Rhode Bytes&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The Unreal Deal&amp;rdquo; two shows on TV that air periodically on Saturday nights on NBC 10 in Rhode Island.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Doreen studied under Stella Adler as a theater major at NYU.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_j9g3a2y1</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_z2qcdpg7</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_ffkzy5rm</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>