<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>motivate_a_problem_employee</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">&lt;span&gt;How to Motivate a Problem Employee&lt;/span&gt;</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harry&amp;rsquo;s worried that Alex&amp;rsquo;s lack of motivation will infect the entire team. He tells Alex to make a to-do list and &amp;ldquo;just put your heart into the work&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;but his effort falls flat. A professional coach suggests finding out what most motivates Alex&amp;mdash;and then tailoring work processes to tap into those motivators.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coach&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sharon Grady&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;is the President of The Grady Company, a consulting firm that provides executives with the communication and conflict-management skills that drive their success as leaders. She specializes in teaching individuals and teams to excel at the challenging conversations they typically avoid or manage ineffectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Before founding The Grady Company, Sharon was a consultant with Monitor and with Mercer Management Consulting, and served as Chief Operating Officer of Interaction Associates, a global provider of collaboration consulting and leadership education. She previously worked on Capitol Hill as a staff aide to U.S. Senator Abraham Ribicoff, and as press secretary to U.S. Congresswoman Barbara Kennelly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sharon holds a Bachelor of Arts in English from Wesleyan University and a Master of Business Administration from Harvard Business School. She studied Advanced Negotiation at Harvard Law School, is a trained mediator, and speaks fluent Spanish. Her website is www.gradycompany.com.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Actors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harry Gordon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; was born in Vermont and began his performing career when he sang &amp;ldquo;Hard-Hearted Hannah&amp;rdquo; to his grandparents at the age of seven. He is a performer, writer, instructor, and comedian who earned his chops at the Improv Asylum in Boston&amp;rsquo;s North End and ImprovBoston in Cambridge. He hosts the critically acclaimed &amp;ldquo;Harry Roasts America!&amp;rdquo; at ImprovBoston and improvises in a variety of shows and troupes, including Directions. He is an active member of the Greater Boston Zen Center and volunteers for a variety of organizations through them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harry has work experience in a variety of fields, including insurance, investment, higher education, consulting, and transportation. He is a Sales Executive at Zipcar in their Zipcar for Business program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Alex LeBaron&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; is an actor, improviser, writer, and instructor currently residing in Chicago. He is a founding member of Rich Uncle and has performed with the sketch groups Whippersnapper, Mosaic, and the Ruckus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Alex has appeared in numerous showcase shows, including: &amp;ldquo;Love Seasonally,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Wheel of Austen,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;T: An MBTA Musical,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;1.21 Jigowatts,&amp;rdquo; Manthorne and the Baron,&amp;rdquo; Gorefests IX and X, and &amp;ldquo;Playbook.&amp;rdquo; He has performed various shows at Duofest, Providence Improv Festival, Del Close Marathon, Philadelphia Improv Festival, and the North Carolina ComedyArts Festival. As First Person Interpreter at Bostonian Society, he presented historical materials to crowds of up to 75 in an educational and entertaining manner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Alex received his Bachelor of Arts in international affairs and political science at the University of New Hampshire. He studied Spanish language and literature at the Pontificia Universidad Cat&amp;oacute;lica de Valpara&amp;iacute;so.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_hycvw9q9</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_3uvy6m88</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_sfptylyy</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>