<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>negotiate_interests_not_positions</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;Negotiate Interests, Not Positions&lt;/p&gt;</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;Robert&amp;rsquo;s negotiating a contract with Harry, a rep for a key vendor. Harry won&amp;rsquo;t budge on his pricing, so they&amp;rsquo;re at an impasse. A professional coach advises Robert to find out what&amp;rsquo;s motivating Harry to stick to the price he named. With this understanding, Robert can open up more possibilities for making a deal.&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;Coach&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Audrey J. Lee&lt;/b&gt; is the Boston-based Principal of consulting firm Perspectiva. She is an experienced trainer specializing in communication, diversity issues, and conflict management. A certified mediator, Audrey helps clients manage critical relationships successfully. Past clients include Novo Nordisk, Desutche Bank, and the Illinois Supreme Court, where she designed and facilitated courses on diversity, communication skills, and professionalism. Perspectiva has had a long-term collaboration with the Harvard Negotiation Project, an ongoing effort to improve negotiation skills through real-world conflict intervention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before joining Perspectiva, Audrey worked as an intellectual property and litigation attorney at Winston &amp;amp; Strawn in Chicago and Davis Polk &amp;amp; Warwell in New York.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She lives in Boston and is an instructor both in the Harvard Negotiation Institute and lecturer at University of Massachusetts Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She is a graduate of Harvard College and Harvard Law School.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Robert Woo&lt;/b&gt; is the Marketing Manager at InsightSquared. A student of viral marketing and comedy, his goal is to mesh these two aspects at every turn in his professional career. Robert tries comedy in improv currently with Hard Left Productions, and stand-up currently in front of a mirror. He writes sketches and web series; acts for various commercials; directs improv off and on; and plays the guitar just enough to maintain his calluses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robert has performed in various festivals in Boston, Lowell, Chicago, New York, Providence, Sarasota, Tokyo, Atlanta, Lowell, Vancouver, and Austin.Robert studied at Tufts University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Harry Gordon&lt;/b&gt; was born in Vermont and began his performing career when he sang &amp;ldquo;Hard-Hearted Hannah&amp;rdquo; to his grandparents at the age of seven. He is a performer, writer, instructor, and comedian who earned his chops at the Improv Asylum in Boston&amp;rsquo;s North End and ImprovBoston in Cambridge. He hosts the critically acclaimed &amp;ldquo;Harry Roasts America!&amp;rdquo; at ImprovBoston and improvises in a variety of shows and troupes, including Directions. He is an active member of the Greater Boston Zen Center and volunteers for a variety of organizations through them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harry has work experience in a variety of fields, including insurance, investment, higher education, consulting, and transportation. He is a Sales Executive at Zipcar in their Zipcar for Business program.&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_gprzux6e</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_jfopax9q</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_k6m1iglf</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>