<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>provide_balanced_feedback_on_employees_performance</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">&lt;span&gt;Provide Balanced Feedback on Employees&amp;rsquo; Performance&lt;/span&gt;</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; During Tao&amp;rsquo;s annual performance review, Christine raves about his achievements, then tells him his overall rating is average. He&amp;rsquo;s disappointed, and she doesn&amp;rsquo;t know why. A professional coach explains that if an employee has strengths and improvement opportunities, you need to balance praise with constructive feedback. That way, the performance rating has meaning, and the employee knows what to focus on next.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coach&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jeni Harnden-Koehler&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;is founder and President of Talent Acceleration Group. As an executive, she manages assessing, developing, integrating, and coaching senior leaders and teams. At a team level, she specializes in improving team functioning using action learning interventions that build the leadership skills of individuals. Jeni has a special interest in developing women leaders, which is expressed in her engagement with the Women&amp;rsquo;s Network Advisory Board of the Greater Boston Chamber of Commerce and Simmons&amp;rsquo;s Women&amp;rsquo;s Initiative. Committed to the evolution of the talent management profession, Jeni serves on the Steering Committee of the New Talent Management Network&amp;ndash;Boston City Group and is involved with the OD Network. She continues her commitment to development as a coach through her affiliation with the Institute of Coaching at Harvard Medical School as well as the International Consortium for Coaching in Organizations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Formerly Vice President of Talent Management at Fidelity investments, Jeni focused on the development of high-potentials and senior executives across the enterprise. She assisted business leaders and HR partners in all areas of talent management, including talent review and succession planning, performance management, leadership development, and management training. Companies that she supported during this time include Gillette/P&amp;amp;G, Duracell, Braun, BestBuy, Exelon, Public Service New Hampshire (PSNH), Standard Register, Steelcase, and Federated Department Stores.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jeni graduated from Smith College with a BA in psychology. She received a PhD in psychology from Harvard University.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Actors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Christine Cuddy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;, who prefers to be called by her last name, is a seasoned actress. She grew up in the Boston area, where she trained in the performing arts. She also learned her trade at the Second City and Annoyance theaters in Chicago. She performs with the Mainstage cast and teaches improv at ImprovBoston. She writes and performs in OBV!, a two-woman show with Megan Goltermann, and has appeared in regional commercials. Christine can be heard on the ImprovBoston podcast with Will Luera and Harry Gordon. Her favorite festival experience is performing in the Improv Allstar Show with Rachel Dratch at the Women in Comedy Festival in Boston. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other ImprovBoston credits include &amp;ldquo;Cabin Pressure,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The A-Team,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Real Housewives of the Magick Kingdom,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The Lodge,&amp;rdquo; a three-person show that plays to her biggest strength--being a townie. Christine has performed at improv festivals all over the United States, Ireland, and Spain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Christine graduated from Framingham State University with a degree in communication arts with a focus in acting and directing&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tao Yang&lt;/b&gt; does everything that interests him with the flourish and dedication of a wonk, meaning that he is a data-wonk, improv-wonk, and computer-wonk. Tao is one of the hardest-working young comedy improvisers in the field. By day he is a data analyst at a healthcare information services company. By night he performs at ImprovBoston.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tao started doing improv with Boston University&amp;rsquo;s Liquid Fun and taking classes at ImprovBoston. He graduated from BU and from ImprovBoston. He has been selected to join the cast of &amp;ldquo;Face Off,&amp;rdquo; and appears with his ImprovBoston team at Big Gulp 40 on the weekends. When he has the time, his usual schedule of studying, performing, and learning improv often consumes eight hours of his day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;ldquo;My approach to comedy is to never stop learning.&amp;rdquo; Tao seems to be living up to his own words on the subject.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_0gatfdam</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_wyjw36ox</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_nu4sjjni</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>