<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>set_clear_goals_for_employees_before_performance_appraisals</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">Set Clear Goals for Employees Before Performance Appraisals</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;During a
performance review, Brendan tells Natalie she&amp;rsquo;s not recruiting enough new
clients. To his surprise, she&amp;rsquo;s surprised by the criticism. A professional
coach warns Brendan against assuming employees can infer what&amp;rsquo;s expected of
them&amp;mdash;and advises him to communicate expectations clearly on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;Coach&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jeni Harnden-Koehler&lt;/b&gt; is founder and President of Talent Acceleration Group. As an executive, she manages assessing, developing, integrating, and coaching senior leaders and teams. At a team level, she specializes in improving team functioning using action learning interventions that build the leadership skills of individuals. Jeni has a special interest in developing women leaders, which is expressed in her engagement with the Women&amp;rsquo;s Network Advisory Board of the Greater Boston Chamber of Commerce and Simmons&amp;rsquo;s Women&amp;rsquo;s Initiative. Committed to the evolution of the talent management profession, Jeni serves on the Steering Committee of the New Talent Management Network&amp;ndash;Boston City Group and is involved with the OD Network. She continues her commitment to development as a coach through her affiliation with the Institute of Coaching at Harvard Medical School as well as the International Consortium for Coaching in Organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Formerly Vice President of Talent Management at Fidelity investments, Jeni focused on the development of high-potentials and senior executives across the enterprise. She assisted business leaders and HR partners in all areas of talent management, including talent review and succession planning, performance management, leadership development, and management training. Companies that she supported during this time include Gillette/P&amp;amp;G, Duracell, Braun, BestBuy, Exelon, Public Service New Hampshire (PSNH), Standard Register, Steelcase, and Federated Department Stores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeni graduated from Smith College with a BA in psychology. She received a PhD in psychology from Harvard University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brendan Mulhern&lt;/b&gt; is an actor, improviser, and musician. He has worked with ImprovBoston since 2008 and is currently a member of their National Touring Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brendan co-created the two-man improv show &amp;ldquo;Manthorne and The Baron,&amp;rdquo; which ran during ImprovBoston&amp;rsquo;s Comedy Lab.&amp;nbsp; The production became a Showcase Show featured at Philly Duofest, Del Close Marathon in New York City, and the 3rd Annual Boston Comedy Arts Festival. His Boston theater credits include: &amp;ldquo;The Haberdasher: A Tale of Derring-Do, &amp;ldquo;The Seabirds&amp;rdquo; (Argos Productions); &amp;ldquo;Deathtrap&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Money Python&amp;rsquo;s Spamalot&amp;rdquo; (The Company Theater); and &amp;ldquo;T: An MBTA Musical&amp;rdquo; (A.R.T./Club Oberon). Film credits include &amp;ldquo;A Terrible Idea&amp;rdquo; (MMM Productions) and &amp;ldquo;The Heebie-Jeebies&amp;rdquo; (Dust Bunny Productions).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Natalie Baseman is a comedian and a lady. She began writing and performing comedy professionally at ImprovBoston with the comedy groups Maxitor and The Dowry. She is pursuing an MFA in Writing for Screen and Television at the University of Southern California&amp;rsquo;s School of Cinematic Arts in Los Angeles. She is involved with Abso Lutely Productions and Comedy Bang! Bang! at the University of Southern California.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Natalie has studied with teachers from the Annoyance, I.O., Upright Citizen&amp;rsquo;s Brigade, and Second City, including Mick Napier. While living in Edinburgh, she worked with the Edinburgh Improverts and the Parisian movement theater company, Dancing Brick. She also wrote/directed the solo sketch comedy show &amp;ldquo;Part Toaster/Part Worm,&amp;rdquo; which she has performed in Boston and Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_rmj6kuan</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_8lidcnd8</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_hzvln30b</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>