<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>stay_open_when_receiving_feedback</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="true"/><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mike&amp;rsquo;s just given a great presentation. So he&amp;rsquo;s shocked&amp;mdash;and gets defensive&amp;mdash;when his boss criticizes some aspects of it. A professional coach offers tips for receiving critical feedback&amp;mdash;including treating it as an opportunity to make your good job performance even better.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stevenson Carlebach &lt;/b&gt;is an independent management consultant and trainer who helps clients learn how to communicate, negotiate, and resolve disputes effectively. He has worked extensively with Fortune 500 companies, including Goldman Sachs, BP Amoco, IBM, and Microsoft. His specialties include strategic relationship management, executive coaching, and difficult conversations. He worked with the Israeli Ministry of Education to develop conflict-resolution programming for schools.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior to becoming a consultant, Stevenson was associate professor and Chair of the theater department of Connecticut College, where he founded the Holleran Center for Community Action and Public Policy. The multidisciplinary academic center focuses on teaching, learning, and community collaboration. He currently teaches a course on mediation and conflict resolution within Harvard Law School&amp;rsquo;s Program on Negotiation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stevenson also holds a BA in classics from Tufts University and a Masters in Fine Arts with a specialty in theater directing from Boston University. He is the father of six children.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Actors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Google &amp;ldquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mike Morrell&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;rdquo; and an American politician, a CIA Deputy Director, and a modern mystic come up before Mike Morrell, actor and improviser, comes into view. Any of these characters are subjects Mike could impersonate with ease. He is the creator/director of &amp;ldquo;Crime Solving Bear&amp;rdquo; and the popular &amp;ldquo;DWA Presents,&amp;rdquo; better known as &amp;ldquo;The Drinking Show.&amp;rdquo; He has filmed over 100 commercials and training videos with roles as varied and diverse as bad nurse, bad paper shredder, and bad employee.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mike has performed improv and stand-up all over Boston, New York, and Los Angeles. He is the cast member of TheartreSports as well as creator and cast member of the showcase show &amp;ldquo;UnAuthorized Biography.&amp;rdquo; He just filmed his first speaking role in a major production.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Robert Woo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; is the Marketing Manager at InsightSquared. A student of viral marketing and comedy, his goal is to mesh these two aspects at every turn in his professional career. Robert tries comedy in improv currently with Hard Left Productions, and stand-up currently in front of a mirror. He writes sketches and web series; acts for various commercials; directs improv off and on; and plays the guitar just enough to maintain his calluses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Robert has performed in various festivals in Boston, Lowell, Chicago, New York, Providence, Sarasota, Tokyo, Atlanta, Lowell, Vancouver, and Austin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Robert studied at Tufts University.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_ng99lcnd</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_teylcigf</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_8p9leiej</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>