<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><asset:playlist xmlns:asset="http://cl.hbsp.org/asset/content" xmlns:alf="http://www.alfresco.org" xmlns:chiba="http://chiba.sourceforge.net/xforms" xmlns:ev="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:ns1="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xf="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><asset:name>while_coaching_listen_more_than_you_talk</asset:name><asset:title xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While Coaching, Listen More Than You Talk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:title><asset:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Doreen wants tech-savvy Marcelo to demo a product for the sales force. He&amp;rsquo;s nervous, so she keeps reassuring him that he&amp;rsquo;ll do fine&amp;mdash;but he&amp;rsquo;s not convinced. A professional coach advises Doreen to listen for the reasons behind Marcelo&amp;rsquo;s fears&amp;mdash;then offer forms of support &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;he &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:description><asset:biography xsi:nil="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coach&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lauren Mackler&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; is an internationally renowned executive and life coach, bestselling author, and keynote speaker. Over the past 25 years she&amp;rsquo;s been a psychotherapist, corporate executive, leader of Arthur Andersen&amp;rsquo;s Human Capital consulting practice, and a leading authority in human behavior, leadership, and professional performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lauren&amp;rsquo;s the author of the international bestseller &amp;ldquo;Solemate: Master the Art of Aloneness &amp;amp; Transform Your Life,&amp;rdquo; and contributor to &amp;ldquo;Speaking of Success&amp;rdquo; with Stephen Covey, Ken Blanchard, and Jack Canfield. Her work is frequently featured in the media, including CNN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;FOX, the Wall Street Journal, the Huffington Post, the London Daily Mail, the Boston Globe, and the Boston Business Journal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Contact Lauren at&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.laurenmackler.com."&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.laurenmackler.com.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Actors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Doreen Collins&lt;/b&gt;&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; show business career began at the tender age of eight in front of 20,000 people, performing with Diana Ross and the Supremes. Since then, she has been an active member of SAG, AFTRA, and AGVA and has performed Off-Broadway and on television, film, and radio. Doreen&amp;rsquo;s one-woman show &amp;ldquo;BOOZICAL the Musical: The Unorganized Biography of Doreen Collins&amp;rdquo; is proof there is nothing that can embarrass her! She lives to perform. She&amp;rsquo;s the host of &amp;ldquo;Rhode Bytes&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The Unreal Deal&amp;rdquo; two shows on TV that air periodically on Saturday nights on NBC 10 in Rhode Island.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Doreen studied under Stella Adler as a theater major at NYU.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Marcelo Illarmo&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;is a member of ImprovBoston. He is also an associate litigation lawyer with Sullivan &amp;amp; Worcester LLP who has represented a variety of clients from small construction firms to Fortune 500 companies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;After performing with Liquid Fun&amp;rsquo;s inaugural cast at Boston University, Marcelo joined Face Off (formerly TheatreSports) before his senior year of college. In addition to performing with Face Off, he has performed in various shows, including a staging of his one-man show, &amp;ldquo;Tales of a Broken Heart.&amp;rdquo; His favorite memories of ImprovBoston include hosting the Sunday Night Jam with JR Strauss and performing an original musical he cowrote in college, &amp;ldquo;Jesus Christ Mega Star.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Marcelo graduated from Boston University with a BA, magna cum laude. He attended the Boston University School of Law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</asset:biography><asset:assetCollection><asset:asset>1_w5cifvq9</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_n256ugon</asset:asset><asset:asset>1_y7xqnvz1</asset:asset></asset:assetCollection></asset:playlist>